<!-- 
 <?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" ?> 
-->
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>KazaKaza Blog</title>
<description>
Updates from KazaKaza. I will be updating this alongside the blog.
</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<link>https://kazakaza.xyz/rss.xml</link>
<!-- LB -->
<item>
<title>Name List Update</title>
<guid>
https://kazakaza.xyz/12082020.html
</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 August 2020</pubDate>
<description>
<p>Well, that didn't last long.</p>
<p>As I've stated before the namelist was something I was creating mainly for work, as I need to name many objects in simulator environments daily. This naming process was more or less standardized lately, and now I don't really need a namelist.</p>
<p>Thus, I will be pushing a final update to the list which brings it up to 170 individual names in 17 categories with 10 names in each category. I've also updated the text formatting within the file for readibility.</p>
<p>As always, feel free to download, use and modify the file in any way you want.</p>
</description>
</item>

<title>KazaKaza Blog</title>
<description>
Updates from KazaKaza. I will be updating this alongside the blog.
</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<link>https://kazakaza.xyz/rss.xml</link>
<!-- LB -->
<item>
<title>I Made A Name List!</title>
<guid>
https://kazakaza.xyz/17072020.html
</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 July 2020</pubDate>
<description>
<p>My job routinely requires me to name certain things (ie. ships for simulation) and thus I made a list of 100 names in 10 categories to pull from. The list includes the names or surnames of real and fictional people (and a dog, and two objects). I have uploaded the file to the website, you can find it under the 'files' page, feel free to use it for whatever purpose. </p>
<p>I may grow the list further in the future, in which case the file will be updated. If it's a particularly big update, I might make another blog post about it as well.</p>
</description>
</item>

<title>KazaKaza Blog</title>
<description>
Updates from KazaKaza. I will be updating this alongside the blog.
</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<link>https://kazakaza.xyz/rss.xml</link>
<!-- LB -->
<item>
<title>First Post!</title>
<guid>
https://kazakaza.xyz/29062020.html
</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020</pubDate>
<description>
<p>Alright, here goes my first ever blog post.</p>
<p>For now, I am editing everything manually, including the rss xml. That's a huge pain so I am looking into solutions. I like the simplicity of this but on the other hand, it's really inconvenient.</p>
<p>Anyway, I will cut it short for the first post, this is about all I wanted to say.</p>
</description>
</item>

</channel>

</rss>
